m 20 0 l 209 0 b 218 0 229 11 229 20 l 229 209 b 229 218 218 228 209 228 l 20 228 b 11 228 0 218 0 209 l 0 20 b 0 11 11 0 20 0
m 115 64 l 115 35 l 171 0 l 177 0 l 133 46 l 143 52 l 179 0 l 184 0 l 159 63 l 229 107 l 229 182 l 145 96 l 135 122 l 207 227 l 137 227 l 115 172 l 115 93 l 126 76 l 115 64 l 104 76 l 115 93 l 115 172 l 93 227 l 23 227 l 95 122 l 84 96 l 0 182 l 0 107 l 70 63 l 45 0 l 50 0 l 87 52 l 97 46 l 52 0 l 59 0 l 115 35
m 325 0 l 355 0 l 332 47 l 354 47 l 399 136 l 369 136 l 328 53 l 288 136 l 257 136 l 325 0 m 467 0 l 497 0 l 474 47 l 496 47 l 541 136 l 511 136 l 470 53 l 430 136 l 399 136 l 467 0 m 545 1 l 583 1 l 583 14 l 568 14 l 568 19 l 583 19 l 583 30 l 568 30 l 568 34 l 599 34 l 599 30 l 583 30 l 583 19 l 599 19 l 599 14 l 583 14 l 583 1 l 611 1 b 616 1 622 6 622 10 l 622 36 l 652 0 l 678 0 l 644 41 l 622 41 l 622 47 l 596 47 l 597 54 l 625 54 l 625 68 l 541 68 l 541 54 l 572 54 l 571 47 l 545 47 l 545 1 m 583 72 l 583 85 l 569 85 l 569 90 l 598 90 l 598 85 l 583 85 l 583 72 l 611 72 b 615 72 621 78 621 82 l 653 44 l 678 44 l 644 86 l 621 86 l 621 103 l 597 103 l 597 136 l 570 136 l 564 126 l 562 136 l 542 136 l 548 107 l 568 107 l 565 121 l 571 121 l 571 103 l 547 103 l 547 72 l 583 72 m 600 107 l 620 107 l 624 124 l 653 89 l 679 89 l 642 136 l 615 136 l 618 132 l 606 132 l 600 107 m 689 0 l 716 0 l 721 15 l 732 15 l 732 30 l 718 56 l 731 56 l 735 100 l 721 100 l 717 59 l 714 64 l 714 136 l 693 136 l 693 79 l 676 79 l 707 30 l 679 30 l 679 15 l 694 15 l 689 0 m 738 0 l 804 0 b 807 0 813 6 813 9 l 813 87 l 794 87 l 794 14 l 756 14 l 756 87 l 763 77 l 763 21 l 787 21 l 787 91 l 798 91 l 798 120 l 820 120 l 812 136 l 778 136 l 778 90 l 748 136 l 723 136 l 756 87 l 738 87 l 738 0 m 257 151 l 275 151 l 297 182 l 319 151 l 337 151 l 304 197 l 304 227 l 290 227 l 290 197 l 257 151 m 337 151 l 355 151 l 377 182 l 399 151 l 417 151 l 384 197 l 384 227 l 370 227 l 370 197 l 337 151 m 425 192 l 447 192 b 445 181 427 181 425 192 l 410 192 b 414 162 458 162 462 192 l 462 206 l 425 206 b 425 210 429 212 433 213 l 462 213 l 462 227 l 433 227 b 412 227 408 203 410 192 m 462 151 l 532 151 l 532 165 l 504 165 l 504 227 l 489 227 l 489 165 l 462 165 l 462 151 m 580 172 l 580 186 l 549 186 b 543 186 543 192 549 192 l 565 192 b 589 192 589 227 565 227 l 532 227 l 532 213 l 565 213 b 570 213 570 206 565 206 l 549 206 b 524 206 524 172 549 172 l 580 172 m 592 213 l 606 213 l 606 227 l 592 227 l 592 213 m 639 172 l 665 172 l 665 186 l 639 186 b 623 186 623 213 639 213 l 665 213 l 665 227 l 639 227 b 603 227 603 172 639 172 m 700 184 b 722 184 722 215 700 215 l 700 229 b 740 229 740 170 700 170 b 660 170 660 229 700 229 l 700 215 b 680 215 680 184 700 184 m 737 172 l 782 172 b 803 172 813 177 813 198 l 813 228 l 799 228 l 799 198 b 799 186 793 187 782 187 l 782 228 l 768 228 l 768 187 l 752 187 l 752 228 l 737 228 l 737 172
本字幕由人人影视字幕组翻译
禁止用作任何商业盈利行为
翻译  冰蓝
翻译  蘑菇
翻译  Marshal同学
翻译  重案组李Sir
翻译  CS小明漫画家
翻译  爱卿遛小鸟
翻译  小饭
翻译  送小孩
翻译  卫老哥
校对  送小孩  卫老哥
校对  Lemony  米小勒
时间轴  加森  marktaotao
时间轴  雪贵人
特效/后期  、青衣
特效/后期  吉吉
总监  送小孩
行尸走肉
第四季  第九集
卡尔  慢点
Carl, slow down.
卡尔  站住
Carl, stop!
我们得待在一起
We need to stay together.
我们得找到有食物和补给的地方
We got to find a place with food, supplies.
我们会...
We're gonna be...
老乔和小乔的烧烤屋
在外面等着  好吗
Wait outside, okay?
-你放哨  -你才应该放哨
- Keep watch. - You keep watch.
你站都站不稳
You can barely stand.
我不会让你自己进去的
I'm not gonna let you go in there alone.
-你说什么  -我们以前这样做过
- Excuse me? - We've done this before.
我来帮你清场
I'm gonna help you clear it.
你该让我一个人做这事
You should just let me do it myself.
进吧
Let's go.
厨房安全
Kitchen's clear.
小乔的特别辣酱
可能只剩那些了
That might be all that's left.
-我可以从这里打死它  -不
- I can get it from here. - No.
不  它很虚弱
No, it's weak.
我引它出去
I'll draw it out.
请完成
我未能
做到的事
- 小乔
后退
Stay back.
该死
Damn it.
别开枪
Don't.
我说了别开枪
I said not to.
你没法用斧子杀死它
You couldn't do it with the ax.
我能干掉它
I had it.
每颗子弹都很重要
Every bullet counts.
如果你回头需要那颗子弹呢
What if you needed that one later?
看看能找到什么  然后我们就走
See what you can find. Then let's move on.
幸好厨房不是空的
Kitchen wasn't empty after all.
这是我找到的  你呢
My haul. You?
我赢了
I win.
这间也不赖
That one's as good as any.
-卡尔  -我搞的定
- Carl. - I got it.
所有的门都是开着的
All the doors down here are open.
停下
Just stop!
来呀  混蛋
Hey, asshole!
来呀  傻逼
Hey, shitface!
-来呀  -别爆粗
- Hey- - Watch your mouth!
你开玩笑吧
Are you kidding me?
如果有行尸  早就出来了
If there's one of them down there, they would have come out.
我把门系死了
I tied the door shut.
我们不能冒险
We don't need to take any chances.
你觉得不够牢吗
You don't think it'll hold?
-卡尔  -这个结很结实
- Carl. - It's a strong knot.
双套结  肖恩教我的
Clove hitch. Shane taught me.
记得他吗
Remember him?
是的  我记得他
Yeah, I remember him.
我每天都会记起他
I remember him every day.
你还有什么话想对我说吗
There something else you want to say to me?
撑过今晚应该没问题
This'll have to do for the night.
你想来点吗
You gonna have some?
你应该吃点东西
You should eat.
我们应该存着
We should save it.
我不想吃
I don't want any.
赶紧吃了
Eat it.
现在就吃
Now.
听着  我只是实话实说
Listen. I'm just being honest.
我觉得有点平淡
I thought it was a bit... pedestrian.
-平淡  -也就是说无趣
- Pedestrian? - As in lame.
-而且俗套  -俗套吗
- And played. - Played?
你之前在哪里见过  说说看
Where have you seen anything like it before? Tell me that.
我从没见过一只大猩猩开车
I've never seen a gorilla drive a car before,
但即使你将其陈列于博物馆中
but if you put it in a museum,
我也不觉得那是艺术
I'm not gonna call it art.
麦克  你能跟你家亲爱的讲讲道理吗
Mike, would you please talk some sense into your lover?
上帝啊  别那样称呼我
Oh, my God. You did not just call me that.
我同意我家亲爱的观点
I agree with my lover.
-我也觉得这...  -非常无趣
- I mean, the whole thing was-- - Very lame.
-而且非常俗套  -等等  等等
- And very played. - Oh, wait, wait, wait.
不不不  别这样  不要这样
No, no, don't do that. Don't do that.
你俩这样一唱一和
Don't start finishing each other's sentences, man.
特恶心
This is just gross.
我想说的是  整体感觉就像
I was going to say that the whole thing was like a monument to
某人竭尽全力想标新立异
someone trying too damned hard to be different.
哈利路亚
Hallelujah.
听着  我很高兴自己看了
Listen, I'm glad I saw it
虽然我并不喜欢
even though I did not love it.
希望我们没有烦到你  小可爱
Hope we're not boring you, peanut.
快过来
Come here.
我们不能在营地久留
I don't think that we should stay at the camp.
不  我不会把儿子带出去
No. I'm not taking my son out there.
我不敢肯定这地方是否安全
I don't know if this place will work out,
但我敢肯定外面一定不安全
but I know it won't if we go out there.
这一切还有什么意义吗
Does it even matter anymore?
我们是在自欺欺人吗
Are we just kidding ourselves?
好吧
Okay.
我明白是怎么回事了
All right, I see what this is.
真的吗
Really?
那你倒说说看啊  米琼恩
What is this, Michonne?
你善于用剑
I mean, you've gotten good with a sword.
你知道这本事现在多有价值吗
You know how valuable that is now?
-你知道那让你多重要吗  -那又有何用
- You know what that makes you? - For what?
生存的目标在哪里
What are we going for?
幸福的结局在哪里
Where's the happy ending here?
这根本就不是生活
This isn't life.
完全算不上  知道吗
This isn't anything close, okay?
对我不是  对我们不是
Not for me, not for us.
对我们的儿子也不是
And for our son.
答案到底是什么
What's the answer here?
你他妈到底想问什么  麦克
Well, what is the damn question, Mike?
为什么
Why?
好吧
Okay.
很好
That's good.
现在我有个问题
Now I have a question.
谁把这瓶酒给开了
Who's gonna open the wine?
不  不
No. No.
不  不  不  不
No, no, no, no.
不  不
No. No!
不  不  不  不
No! No! No! No!
不
No!
为了胜利
爸
Dad?
爸  醒醒
Dad, wake up.
醒醒  快点
Wake up. Come on.
爸  醒醒  醒醒
Dad, wake up. Wake up.
醒醒  醒醒
Wake up! Wake up!
快醒醒
Wake up!
你们
Hey, you!
这里有新鲜的肉  过来吃
Fresh meat right here. Come and get it.
一起走一走吧
Let's take a walk.
跟上
Keep up.
就是这样
That's it.
继续
Keep coming.
很好
Very good.
快点  跟上
Come on, keep coming.
快点
Come on.
就在这儿  看着我
Right here, look at me.
很好
There you go.
快点
Come on.
就是这样
That's it.
该死
Oh, shit.
我赢了
I win.
真酷
Cool.
我杀了三个行尸
I killed three walkers.
它们在门口
They were at the door.
快进来了
They were gonna get in,
但是
but
我引开了它们
I lured them away.
我干掉了它们
I killed them.
我救了你
I saved you.
你让大家种地的时候  我没有丢掉技能
I didn't forget while you had us playing farmer.
我还记得如何生存
I still know how to survive.
算我们走运
Lucky for us.
我不再需要你了
I don't need you anymore.
我不需要你来保护我了
I don't need you to protect me anymore.
我可以照顾好自己
I can take care of myself.
你也许根本就保护不了我
You probably can't even protect me anyways.
你没能保护好朱迪思
You couldn't protect Judith.
你没能保护好...
You couldn't protect...
赫谢尔  格伦
Hershel or Glenn
玛姬
or Maggie.
米琼恩  达里尔
Michonne, Daryl,
还有妈妈
or Mom.
你只想种菜
You just wanted to plant vegetables.
你只想躲起来
You just wanted to hide.
他知道我们在哪  但你却不在意
He knew where we were and you didn't care!
你只是躲在围栏后面坐以待毙
You just hid behind those fences and waited for...
大家现在都没了
They're all gone now.
都是因为你
Because of you!
他们指望着你
They counted on you!
你是他们的领袖
You were their leader!
但是现在
But now...
你什么都不是了
you're nothing.
你死了我也会很好
I'd be fine if you died.
该死
Damn it.
妈的
Oh, shit.
滚开
Come on.
快
快啊
Come on.
滚开
萨姆
里面的行尸抢走了我的鞋
但没抓到我
不
No!
不  不
No. No.
不  不  不
No! No! No! No!
我做不到
I can't.
我错了
I was wrong.
动手吧
Just do it.
卡尔
Carl.
别出去
Don't go outside.
注意安全
Stay safe.
我害怕
I'm scared.
请完成我未能做到的事  小乔
麦克
Mike.
我想你
I miss you.
跟你在一起时也想你
I missed you even when I was with you.
在营地时
Back at the camp.
做出那事的人不是你
It wasn't you who did it.
你错了
You were wrong.
因为我还活着
Because I'm still here.
你本来也可以
And you could be, too.
他也可以
And he could be.
我知道答案了
I know the answer.
我知道为什么了
I know why.
老乔和小乔的烧烤屋
你不该冒险
You shouldn't have risked it,
像那样出去
going out there like that.
这很危险
It's dangegerou.
我很小心
I was careful.
还好你找到了很多食物
It's good that you found more food.
本来有更多
I found even more.
但我吃了
But I ate it.
那是什么
What was it?
六斤的布丁
112 ounces of pudding.
我知道
I know...
我们永远不可能让一切回到从前
we'll never get things back to the way they used to be.
什么
What?
我之前那样做全是为了你
I only clung to that for you.
为了朱迪思
For Judith.
但现在她离去了
Now she's gone.
而你
And you...
你是个男人了  卡尔
you're a man, Carl.
你是个男人了
You're a man.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
你不必抱歉
You don't need to be.
巧克力布丁
怎么了
What?
是来找你的
It's for you.